Guide to the New-York Historical Society Poster Collection 1790-2022 PR 55
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. World's Fair and Other Fairs Posters, 1854-1965; 40 item(s)
  - "Come back to the Fair" New York's World's Fair, 1961 (Folder FF 04-06)
    3 copies. "Unisphere presented by United States Steel copyrighted 1961, 1962 New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Corporation" Printed by Allied Printing, Philadelphia. On back of all copies stamped, "This publication was presented to this Library by Peter M. Warner."
  - "New York World's Fair 1964-1965", 1961 (Folder FF 04-06)
    3 copies. Poster designed by B. Peak. "Unisphere presented by United States Steel copyrighted 1961, 1962 New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Corporation". Printed by Amalgamated Lithographers of America, New York -- "Litho in U.S.A." Stamped on back of all copies, "This publication was presented to this Library by Peter M. Warner".
  - "Come back to the Fair!" New York World's Fair, 1961 (Folder FF 04-06)
    3 copies. "Unisphere presented by United States Steel copyrighted 1961 New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Corporation" Printed by Allied Printing, Philadelphia. Stamped on back of all copies, "This publication was presented to this Library by Peter M. Warner".
  - "New York World's Fair 1964-1965", 1961 (Folder FF 04-06)
    6 copies (2 mounted on cardboard with easel backs). Poster designed by B. Peak. "Unisphere presented by United States Steel copyrighted 1961, 1962 New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Corporation". Printed by Amalgamated Lithographers of America, New York -- "Litho in U.S.A." Stamped on back of some copies, "This publication was presented to this Library by Peter M. Warner".
  - "Texas Pavilions. Music Hall.", c.1961 (Folder FF 04-06)
    Photograph of Texas Pavilions model. Stamped on back, "This publication was presented to this Library by Peter M. Warner".
- Series V. Political Posters, 1840-2008; 100 item(s) (approximately)
  The collection consists of presidential campaign posters, as well as local political campaign ephemera and posters (mainly New York City and State).
  - Subseries V.1 National Elections, 1840-2008
    - Tippecanoe (Harrison & Tyler) Log Cabin by Whigs of Buffalo, 1840 (Folder FF 05-01)
      Pub & Lith by Hall & Mooney. Poster features a 20x30 foot log cabin erected on March 18, 1840 by the Whigs of Buffalo and dedicated to the cause, Harrison & Tyler.
    - "Log Cabin Anecdotes. Illustrated Incidents in the life of Gen. William Henry Harrison", 1840 (Folder FF 05-01)
      J.F. Trow, Printer. Published by J.P. Giffing.
    - The 12th Ward Democratic Clay Club (Clay & Frelinghuysen), 1844 (Folder FF 05-01)
      M.Hopper Mott was president of the 12th Ward Democratic Clay Club. C.L. Carter, C.S. Miller, Marcellus Eells, and C.M. Graham, Jr. were officers.The event was held at Temerance Hall on 8th Avenue.
    - The Presidential (and Vice Presidential) Candidates. 1856 (Folder FF 05-01)
      Published by B.H. Day. "Brother Jonathan" Weekly Newspaper. Features 3 portraits of the Presidential candidates: Buchanan drawn by S.F. Baker, Fremont Holcombs, and Filmore drawn by Edmonds. And 3 portraits of the Vice-Presidential candidates: Breckenridge drawn by J.W. Orr, Dayton drawn by Holcombs, and Donelson, unsigned.
    - "Scene in the Park July 1860 between Genet and Kerrigan...For County Clerk Harry Genet., 1861 (Folder FF 05-02)
      Note on back explains that poster is a "Hand Bill against Harry W. Genet. November Election 1861"
    - "Lincoln and Johnson!", 1864 (Folder FF 05-02)
      Printed at the Village Record Office, West Chester, PA. Invitation to a meeting at Kennett Square held by the Committee of Vigilance (Dr. Frank Taylor & John J. Pinkerton, Esq.) to prepare for General and Presidential Elections.
    - National Republican Platform of 1868 (Grant & Colfax) (Folder FF 05-02)
      Published by L. John & Co. Poster features portraits of Grant and Colfax and sets out the Republican Platform as adopted at Chicago, May 21, 1868. Acquisition date(?) on front in pencil, May [19]06.
    - "You Must Make Your Choice." (Grant & Colfax), 1868 (Folder FF 05-02)
      2 copies. Designed by V. Miller; published by Photo-Eng. Co., N.Y. Features portraits of Washington, Lincoln, and Grant with the slogan, "National Unity." Copy 1 has acquisition date(?) on front in pencil, May 15/[19]06. Copy 2 lacks heading and is colored.
    - "National Democratic Banner of Victory, 1868." (Seymour & Blair) (Folder FF 05-02)
      Published by Currier & Ives. Features portraits of Horatio Seymour of New York and Frank P. Blair of Missouri and the slogan, "Peace, Union, and Constitutional Government". Acquisition date(?) on back, Nov. 20, 1928.
    - 'Leaders of the Democratic Party." (Seymour & Blair), 1868 (Folder FF 05-02)
      3 copies. Copy 1, acquisition date(?) on front, April 6/[19]06. Copy 2 stamped on back, New York Historical Society Folks Art Collection, Nov. 17, 1937. Poster features four caricatures drawn by Thomas Nast of "The Rioter Seymour", "The Butcher Forrest", "The Pirate Semmes", and "The Hangman Hampton".
    - Tilden and Reform (Tilden & Hendricks), 1876 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Rev. Chambers and Sidney T. Fairchild, Esq. to address citizens of Casenovia, New York.
    - "Cleveland & Victory! Irving Hall...17th Assembly District.", 1884 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Lists candidates for primary elections of Inspectors and Delegates.
    - "November Scribners. Andrews' History. Regular Nominations" (Cleveland v. Blaine), 1884 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Poster features portraits of Cleveland of New York and Blaine of Maine.
    - "Get Out People! And Rejoice! An Era of Good Times at Hand!" (Cleveland & Hendricks), 1884 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Celebratory parade and torchlight procession on the election of Grover Cleveland & Thomas Hendricks.
    - 1884 Presidential and Vice-Presidential Candidates (Cleveland & Hendricks) (Folder FF 05-03)
      Published by James D. Gill of Springfield, MA. Poster features 4 portraits of Cleveland, Hendricks, Blaine, and Logan.
    - The Nation's Choice...James G. Blaine and John A. Logan, 1884 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Published by H.W. Kelley, Philadelphia. This proof features portraits of Blaine and Logan and the Republican Platform. Acquisition date(?) on front, Dec. 06/[19]06.
    - "Building and Ruling the Republic...The Biographies of Blaine & Logan and Cleveland & Hendricks", 1884 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Poster advertising the political book which was written by James P. Boyd and published by J.C. McCurdy & Co. Publishers, Philadelphia, Cincinnati, Chicago, and St. Louis.
    - "Who Defrauded the American People out of their Choice for President in 1876.", 1884 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Published by J. Edward Ireland, New York. For sale by The Advance Publishing Co. Poster features 12 portraits of J.A. Garfield, J.P. Bradley, O.P. Morton, W. Strong, G. Casenave, S.M. Kenner, G.F. Edmunds, F.T. Frelinghuysen, G.F. Hoar, S.F. Miller, J. Madison Wells, and T.C. Anderson. Acquisition date(?) on front, Sept. 21/[19]05.
    - "The Whole Story in a Nutshell! Harrison's Ideas!...Cleveland's Ideas!", 1888 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Published by Yale Publishing Co., N.Y. Poster features portraits of Harrison and Cleveland superimposed on maps of the United States and information on the partys's platforms. Acquisition date(?) on back, Sept. 9, 1949.
    - "Campaign '88 Specimen Sheet. Moss Engraving Co. 535 Pearl St., New York.", 1888 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Published by Moss Engraving Co. Features caricatures of Benjamin Harrison, Levi Morton, Grover Cleveland, and Allan Thurman.
    - "Cleveland's Sweep!! 287 Electoral Votes!!!, 1892 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Poster features caricatures from the Philadelphia Record and the Chicago Globe and articles from the Philadelphia Times, the New York Sun, the New York Tribune, and the Public Ledger.
    - "The Tammany Tiger must go. Let the Tail go with the Hide", 1894 (Folder FF 05-03)
      Small card featuring a tiger's hide on front and a poem to the end of Tammany on the back. Published by the Committee of Seventy.
    - "Mr. Bryan on the Stump.", 1900 (Folder FF 05-04)
      Page 1007 of Harper's Weekly of October 27, 1900. Photographs of Mr. Bryan at Benton Harbor, Michigan, and at Findlay, Ohio.
    - "The Issue -- 1900...Liberty. Justice. Humanity...W.J. Bryan" (Folder FF 05-04)
      Copyright 1900 by Neville Williams, Columbus, Ohio. Published by The Strobridge Lith. Co., Cincinnati, Ohio. Further campaign slogans: "No Imperialism" and "Equal Rights to All...Special Privileges to None."
    - "For President...William Jennings Bryan", undated (Folder FF 05-05)
      "From photo by Walinger, Chicago. Published by Martin B. Brown, Co., New York. Acquisition date(?) on front, in pencil, Dec. 2, 1932.
    - The Social Democratic Party...Eugene V. Debs for President...Ben Hanford for Vice President, 1904 (Folder FF 05-05)
      2 copies. One in color, one in black & white. Copyright 1904 by William Mailly, Secy. Published by Eagle Lithographing Co. Slight variations -- "The Social Democratic Party" (color version), "The Socialist Party" (black & white version). Campaign slogan was "Workingmen of all Countries Unite" (color version), "Workers of the World Unite" (black & white version).
    - "For President Theodore Roosevelt of New York...For Vice President Charles W. Fairbanks of Indiana", c.1904 (Folder FF 05-05)
      Roosevelt photo copyrighted by Pach; Fairbanks photo copyrighted by O.V. Buck. No publisher given but a New York Union label stamp. Acquisitiion date(?) on front, in pencil, Feb. 25, 1943.
    - "The Wizard of Oyster Bay" in The Evening Post Cartoon Section., 1910 (Folder FF 05-05)
      Caricature copyrighted 1910 by New York Evening Post Co. and signed by William H. Walker. Features drawing of Teddy Roosevelt with a cauldron, "Political Expediency", with vapors labelled "Payne-Aldrich Tariff" floating away.
    - Progressive Party "Dollar Bill", 1912 (Folder FF 05-05)
      Charter Membership Certificate 1912 Campaign -- "This is a receipt for one dollar contributed to the campaign fund of the Progressive Party." Teddy Roosevelt for President and Hiram W. Johnson for Vice President. "Signed" by Elou Huntington Hooker, National Treasurer. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Feb. 17, 1938. "Harrold E. Gillingham" stamped on back.
    - Official Ballot for Presidential Election for Ninth Election District, Twenty-Ninth Assembly District, County of New York., 1912 (Folder FF 05-05)
      The 1912 election ballot included candidates from the Democratic Party (Wilson/Marshall), Republican Party (Taft/Sherman), Socialist Party (Debs/Seidel), Independence League Party (No nominees), Prohibition Party (Chafin/Watkins), National Progressive Party (Roosevelt/Johnson), and Socialist Labor Party (Reimer/Gillhaus). On back, "Gift of Charles L. Bernhemer. Sept. 21, 1943."
    - "America Always First" (Harding/Coolidge), 1920 (Folder FF 05-06)
      Copyrighted 1920 by Edmondston Studio, Washington, D.C.
    - "For President Warren G. Harding", 1920 (Folder FF 05-06)
      2 copies. Copyrighted 1920 by Edmondston Studio, Washington D.C. Printed by Alco-Gravure, Inc., New York, Baltimore, St. Louis.
    - "Cox or Harding...'Under Which Flag?'", c.1920 (Folder FF 05-06)
      Compilation of two caricatures published by Ritchey with a New York Lithographers Union stamp. The Cox caricature with a League of Nations flag, signed "after Kromer", was reproduced from "The World" (The Leading Cox Organ). The Harding caricature with an American flag was reproduced from "Harvey's Weekly" (Supporter of Harding).
    - "Welcome...President Warren G. Harding and Vice President Calvin Coolidge", 1921 (Folder FF 05-06)
      From the New York Commercial, The National Business Newspaper, Monday Morning, May 23, 1921 (126th Year, No. 119). Photos of both men by Edmondston Studio of Washington, D.C. Stamped on front, at top, "W. Johnson Quinn Collection, New York Hotels, January 1942". On back, photos of several men surrounding caption: "New York Commercial's 125th Anniversary some of the prominent men who have helped make the dinner a success". Herbert Hoover (Sec. of Commerce) was guest speaker, R.A.C. Smith was Chairman of General Committee, and Charles E. Hughes was Honorary Chairman of General Committee.
    - 1921 New York Sample Ballot for 29th Election District, 2nd Assembly District, 65th Precinct (Folder FF 05-06)
    - "Calvin Coolidge For President", 1924 (Folder FF 05-06)
      Copyrighted by John Doctoro, after Walinger Photo. Printed by Wynkoop Hallenbeck.
    - "Father Knickerbocker Welcomes The Democrats of the Nation", 1924 (Folder FF 05-06)
      Image of Father Knickerbocker by Adolph Treidler. Poster for the Democratic National Convention - New York City - June 1924.
    - "Regular Democratic Nomination for President, Alfred E. Smith of New York, for Vice-President, Joe T. Robinson of Arkansas", 1928 (Folder FF 05-06)
      Published by M.B. Brown Printing and Binding Co., N.Y. Campaign slogan: "Honest. Able. Fearless." Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 24, 1928.
    - "The Dawn of Victory...Re-Elect Herbert Hoover", 1932 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Poster features illustration by Howard Chandler Christy. Stamped Allied Printing, New York City.
    - "America...To Our President" Birthday Ball, 1934 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Poster advertising President Roosevelt's Birthday Ball at the Waldorf-Astoria. Features an illustration by Howard Chandler Christy.
    - "Primary Election May 19th...Vote for these Republican Candidates", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Sample ballot was paid for by Monmouth Republican Minute Men. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 20, 1936.
    - "Sham Prosperity!...Vote for Landon and Knox...", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Issued by Campaign Committee Women's National Republican Club, Inc. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - "Citizens of United States...Save America with your Vote for Landon...", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
    - "Today is Lawyers' Day...Landon-Knox Clubs of Greater New York...", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Issued by William Ziegler, Jr., Director, Landon-Knox Clubs of Greater New York. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pen, Nov. 28, 1936.
    - "Your Vote under this American Labor Party emblem counts for Roosevelt and Lehman...", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      2 copies. Published by Signal Press, Inc. Issued by American Labor Party. On both copies - Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 2, 1936. Copy 2 in plastic sleeve with another flyer -- "They Hate Him Because He Gave Labor a Break!" (Roosevelt/Lehman).
    - "Don't be a Scab at the Ballot Box ... Counts for Roosevelt and Lehman...", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Published by Signal Press, Inc. Issued by American Labor Party.
    - "Young Voters ... when you fire your first Ballot ... Counts for Roosevelt and Lehman...", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Published by Signal Press, Inc. Issued by American Labor Party. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Oct. 28, 1936.
    - "Communism on Stage", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Leaflet about "Triple A, Plowed Under" presented by the "living newspaper" unit of The Federal Theater Project. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pen, Oct. 31, 1936.
    - "The Real Roosevelt", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Circular letter issued by The National Republican Builders, Inc. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, April 26, 1937.
    - "A Vote for Roosevelt is a Vote to Continue this Alien Rule! Roosevelt's Supreme Council", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Copyrighted 1936 by Robert Edward Edmondson. Published by Edmondson Economic Service, N.Y. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Aug. 10, 1936.
    - "The Patriotic Crusade Against Jewish Anti-Americanism", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Written by The Edmondson Economic Service - Robert Edward Edmoondson, Sole Proprietor. Copyrighted 1936 by Robert Edward Edmondson. Published by Edmondson Economic Service, N.Y. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Aug. 10, 1936.
    - "Wake Up! Wake Up! For God's Sake -- Wake Up! Your Country Needs You!", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      By Robert Edward Edmondson. Published by Edmondson Economic Service, N.Y. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Aug. 10, 1936.
    - "Landon Knox GOP", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Lithographed by McCandlish Lithograph Corporation, Philadelphia. Features daisy with elephant labelled GOP in center with "Landon" above and "Knox" below. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - Leaflets from the Republican Service League of Chicago, 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      3 leaflets. First entitled "A Veteran Suggest ... A Contrast". Second entitled "Where Do We Go From Here? ... And Now..." Third entitled "I Hate War or I Hate Warriors?". All three leaflets support the Landon/Knox Campaign. On all 3 leaflets, acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - "The Great American Game...Find-The-Goat (Growing National Debt), 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Copyrighted 1936 by The Budd Co., Providence, Rhode Island. The game piece consists of two cardboard discs attached so that the bottom disc can spin with a slot opening in the top disc where spin result can be read. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - "Our Objectives are Clear...Elect...Landon...Knox...", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Flyer printed by The Republican Service League National Headquarters, Chicago. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - Landon and Knox poem against New Deal, 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Anit-New Deal poem by "American Citizen". Not copyrighted - Reproduction invited. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - "Landon Decries Bigotry!...Letter from William Allen White", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Letter was from W.A. White, Editor and Owner of The Emporia Gazette, Emporia, Kansas. Reprinted by Republican National Committee, Eastern Division, New York. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - "Don't Scab at the Ballot Box! To all WPA workers..." (Thomas/Nelson, Socialist Party), 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Flyer issued by the WPA Committee for Thomas and Nelson. Acquisition date(?) on back and front, in pencil, Oct. 31, 1936.
    - "To All Unemployed, WPA Workers and Trade-Unionists! The Socialist Party..." (Thomas/Nelson), 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Invitation leaflet to hear Norman Thomas and David Lasser (Natl. Pres. of the Workers Alliance) speak at Madison Square Garden. Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Oct. 31, 1936.
    - Official General Election Sample Ballot, Belmar Borough, Election District No. 2, 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      "Marked" for Socialist Party.
    - "Landon Volunteers" postcard, 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Postcard signing up volunteers to be sent to Mrs. Preston Davie, Women's Division, Republican National Committee, New York City.
    - "Roosevelt and Lehman Monster Rally Tonight", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Flyer printed by Artisan Press, Union Printers, Brooklyn, N.Y. Under the Auspices of Kings Highway Democratic Club, Inc.
    - "Landon Tells America - I want no support from Bigots", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      2 copies. Flyer issued by Republican National Committee. Stamped Allied Printing, New York City. On both copies - Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Nov. 19, 1936.
    - "Russians for Roosevelt", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Flyer consists of 3 reprinted articles re: Moscow backing Roosevelt. Articles from Chicago Tribune Press Service, Denver Post, and Facts and Opinions.
    - "Reed's Address Denouncing Roosevelt 'Royalism'", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      "Reprinted by permission, New York American, Sept. 4, 1936" Acquisition date(?) on back, in pencil, Oct. 17, 1936.
    - "Landon Leaps into Big Lead", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Reprinted from The Washington Post Weekly News Magazine.
    - Vote for Landon and Knox", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Campaign poster features photographs of each man (stamped "I.P.E.U."). Poster stamped Allied Printing, Chicago.
    - "Landon and Knox for US...Deeds...Not Deficits", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      2 copies - one landscape, one portrait. Campaign poster is red, white, and blue with photographs of each man. Stamped "I.P.E.U." "C.H.W.P. Alled Printing, Buffalo, N.Y. On back of portrait copy, in pen, "Mrs. Geo Wilde. Nov. 19, 1936"
    - "Vote for Franklin D. Roosevelt for President", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Bold red letters on white background. Paid for by Walter Reade. Stamped Allied Printing, New York City. On back, in pencil, "Dr. Frederick Griffith. Nov. 20, 1936"
    - Landon Market Basket Club Brown Paper Bag, 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Printed on brown paper bag are the New York retail cost of several grocery items in 1933 and 1936. On back, in pen, "Mrs. Geo Knox. Nov. 19, 1936"
    - "Come! Join our Prairie Band to Washington with Landon and Knox", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Poster features pen and ink drawing by Juliette Laughlin. On back, in pen, "Mrs. Geo. Wilde. Nov. 19, 1936"
    - Republican Rally Madison Square Garden (Landon/Knox), 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Poster printed by Tenny Press, New York City. Rally under the auspices of Republican State Committee. On back, in pen, "Gift of Mrs. Geo. Wilde. Nov. 19, 1936"
    - "From a Typical Prairie State...Alf M. Landon of Kansas", 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Poster features a photograph of Landon, stamped with Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Chicago. On back, in pencil, "Gift of Frederick Griffith. Dec. 17, 1936"
    - Vote for Landon and Knox and the Entire Republican Ticket, 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Poster printed by Tenny Press, New York City. Features 7 photographs(stamped I.P.E.U.) of Republicans running for State offices, including Governor and Lieutenant Governor. On back, in pen, "Mrs. Geo. Wilde. Nov. 19, 1936"
    - Landon Volunteers...A Declaration of Independence by Democrats, 1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Sign-up poster to be returned to Landon Volunteers, West 36th Street, New York City. On back, in pen, "Mrs. Geo. Wilde. Nov. 19, 1936"
    - "Where To?? (quo vadis America?) Beware!, c.1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      Circular letter from "I am neither a Protestant nor a Jew, and I don't belong to any of the political parties..." warning against voting for any of the candidates supported by Father Coughlin. Letterwriter asks that letter be reprinted and passed through neighborhoods throughout the United States.
    - "No Loitering -or-Electioneering", c.1936 (Folder FF 05-07)
      On back, in pencil, "Gift og Dr. Frederic Griffith. July 19, 1938."
    - "The Opening Gun of the 1940 Presidential Campaign...", 1937 (Folder FF 05-08)
      A 7th Edition of a circular published by Hal Walton, Chairman of the Committee of Witnesses (Charles Lindbergh and kidnapping of son). Acquisition date(?), on back, in pencil, Feb. 19, 1937.
    - "We Stand With Roosevelt", 1940 (Folder FF 05-08)
      Small red, white and blue strip with a union printing label. Acquisition date(?), stamped on back, Oct 8 1940.
    - Wendell Willkie Campaign Poster, 1940 (Folder FF 05-08)
      Copyrighted 1940 by Albert T. Reid Syndicate. Features illustrated life story of Wendell L. Willkie drawn by Albert T. Reid. Acquisition date(?) stamped on back, Oct 22, 1940.
    - "For Peace, Preparedness and Prosperity...Wendell Willkie", 1940 (Folder FF 05-08)
      2 copies. Campaign poster features photograph of Willkie (stamped I.P.E.U.) and an Allied Printing, Chicago stamp.
    - Wendell Willkie Campaign Leaflet, 1940 (Folder FF 05-08)
      Leaflet produced by We, the People Willkie Campaign. Leaflet features a photograph of Willkie on front cover and steps in his career on inside pages.